Today I'm given you some gift ideas for Christmas gifts for your uncle.
Now even if your uncle is so hard to shop for because he has everything or you just really don't know his taste, I really don't think that you can go wrong by getting him a pair of slippers.
Most people like to wear slippers and with it being Christmas, it's obviously going to be cooler weather so it's actually a nice gift to keep there feet nice and warm.
I give them every year.
I give this new pair of slippers to every member of my family.
It's my thing, it's what I like to do.
But this year when I was out shopping I actually found something that I haven't seen before and that's memory foam slippers.
So every time that you put your foot in it works very much like the memory foam pillows and mattresses.
It will actually remember your uncles in step and the shape of his foot and how we walks.
It's actually a very personalized, very tailor gift.
This one is micro suede.
It was very economical.
I'm sure they come in a variety of price ranges.
The only thing you're going to need to remember to do is get his shoe size.
You can either ask your parents or your aunt if your uncle is married or you can just go ahead and buy what size you think he might wear.
Be sure to keep the receipt so he can exchange it but honestly I really don't think you can go wrong with something like this.